const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "What is a budget?   ",
    answers: ["A plan to save money over a year",  "A plan to invest money each month", "A plan for managing income and expenses over a specific period of time", "A plan that shows what to spend money on over a specific period of time"],
    correct: "A plan for managing income and expenses over a specific period of time",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which factors make up your total expenses per month? ",
    answers: ["Fixed expenses (i.e. rent) + food cost", "Fixed expenses (i.e. utilities) + flexible expenses (i.e. car payments)", "Disposable income (i.e. car payments)+ elastic costs (i.e. food cost)", "Fixed expenses (i.e. rent) + flexible expenses (i.e. utilities)"],
    correct: "Fixed expenses (i.e. rent) + flexible expenses (i.e. utilities)",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What portion of your money is disposable income?",
    answers: ["Total income - total expenses", "Total income - income tax", "Total income - fixed expenses", "Total income - flexible expenses"],
    correct: "Total income - total expenses",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is qualified to create budgets?",
    answers: [
      "Financial planners",
      "Accountants",
      "Anyone who properly educates themselves",
      "Only wealthy individuals"
    ],
    correct: "Anyone who properly educates themselves",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "What is an interest rate?",
    answers: ["A fixed rate an individual pays on a loan with consistent frequency", "A malleable rate earned on savings accounts", "An amount either paid or earned on a sum of money consistently over a set period of time", "The initial fee an individual pays to invest in a business"],
    correct: "An amount either paid or earned on a sum of money consistently over a set period of time",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which factors affect national interest rates?",
    answers: [
      "Rates are affected by the central bank through monetary policy",
      "Rates are affected by supply and demand",
      "Rates are affected by reserve requirements",
      "Rates are affected by all of these factors"
    ],
    correct: "Rates are affected by all of these factors",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is an Annual Percentage Rate (APR)?',
    answers: ["The cost of borrowing on consumer loans per year", "The yearly interest rate of a bond", "The prime rate offered by banks", "The interest rate subtracted from the discount rate"],
    correct: "The cost of borrowing on consumer loans per year",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "In which situation will the most interest be accrued?",
    answers: ["A fixed interest rate of 1.5%", "A compounding interest rate of 1.5%", "A discount rate of 1.5%", "A fixed interest rate of 1.55%"],
    correct: "A compounding interest rate of 1.5%",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the definition of a savings account?",
    answers: ["A portion of a checking account that an individual doesn’t spend", "A separate account from the checking account held in a bank or credit union", "An account held in in a bank or credit union that accrues interest on the balance", "A 401K"],
    correct: "An account held in in a bank or credit union that accrues interest on the balance",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is a 401K?",
    answers: [
      "A savings account dedicated to retirement",
      "A savings account dedicated to emergencies",
      "A savings account used by nonprofits",
      "A savings account that holds $401,000"
    ],
    correct: "A savings account dedicated to retirement",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "How can employers affect 401Ks?",
    answers: ["Matching contributions", "Contribution limits", "Determination of completion", "Employers don’t affect 401ks"],
    correct: "Matching contributions",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "Many Americans do not have an emergency savings account. What are the risks associated with this?",
    answers: ["A surprise medical complication could cause an individual to acquire debt", "A car accident may drain an individual’s checking account", "A natural disaster may cause residential damage that an individual is unable to afford the repairs for", "These are all risky situations that should convince me to try my hardest to keep a savings account if it is currently within my financial capabilities"],
    correct: "These are all risky situations that should convince me to try my hardest to keep a savings account if it is currently within my financial capabilities",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "How do credit cards work?",
    answers: ["Credit cards all allow an individual to spend an inexhaustible sum of money on the caveat that they eventually pay it back", "Credit cards allow an individual to spend money directly from their checking account", "Credit cards allow individuals to spend an amount of money determined by the associated bank and pay it back in a specified amount of time", "Credit cards allow individuals to spend unlimited sums of money"],
    correct: "Credit cards allow individuals to spend an amount of money determined by the associated bank and pay it back in a specified amount of time",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "Which factor affects an individual's credit score?",
    answers: ["Making payments consistently before a specified deadline", "The amount of time an individual has had a credit card", "Quantity of debt", "All of these factors and more"],
    correct: "All of these factors and more",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "How can an individual realistically avoid falling into the credit-debt cycle?",
    answers: ["Consistently and punctuallypay off credit cards in full", "Use credit cards frequently", "Keep an emergency savings account", "Never use a credit card"],
    correct: "Consistently and punctuallypay off credit cards in full",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "Why would an individual purposefully go into debt?",
    answers: ["Nobody purposefully goes into debt", "Debt isn't under the control of the individual", "Productive debt can turn a profit, but it can also be risky", "All of these answers are correct"],
    correct: "Productive debt can turn a profit, but it can also be risky",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "Which forms are associated with filing for income tax?",
    answers: ["W2", "1099", "1080", "All of these are correct"],
    correct: "All of these are correct",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can you fill out your tax forms and file for a tax return? ",
    answers: ["Using forms from the IRS", "Using software available online", "Both", "Neither"],
    correct: "Both",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do teenagers have to complete a tax return?",
    answers: ["Yes, if they work", "Not if they earned less than $6350 gross during the taxable period", "Yes if they earned at least $1000 net in the taxable period", "No because they’re not adults"],
    correct: "Not if they earned less than $6350 gross during the taxable period",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "Does an individual need to keep track of their income throughout a year to be prepared for tax returns?",
    answers: [
      "No, that's the employer's responsibility",
      "Yes, you should always keep track of your money coming in verses going out",
      "No, the government tracks it",
      "No, the business you work at does your taxes for you"
    ],
    correct: "Yes, you should always keep track of your money coming in verses going out",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the significance of your filing status?',
    answers: ["How close you are to being finished filing", "A score associated with how well you file", "A title that determines the rate at which you're taxed", "Filing status is not associated with taxes"],
    correct: "A title that determines the rate at which you're taxed",
    questionId: "2019778"
  }
  
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
